Guide to the Sylvère Lotringer Papers and Semiotext(e) Archive, 1960-2004 (Bulk 1973-2000) MSS.221
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Photographic Materials, 182612
  - Subseries A: Professional, 182613
    - Dubose, George, undated; 185815 (Box Binder A)
    - Eeva-Interi (Christo), 1981; 185816 (Box Binder A)
      2 8x10
    - Elbers, Johan (Lee Breuer), undated; 185817 (Box Binder A)
    - Elbers, Johan (Dounglas Dunn), 1983; 185818 (Box Binder A)
    - Ferrato, Donna, undated; 185819 (Box Binder A)
      2 black and white contact sheets
    - Freccia, Ilarta (Lee Breuer), undated; 185820 (Box Binder A)
    - Ganahl, Rainer (Sylvere Lotringer), undated; 185821 (Box Binder A)
      4 color 4x6
    - Hartnett, Elaine (Charlemagne Palestine), 1971; 185822 (Box Binder A)
    - Johnson, Craig, 1985; 185823 (Box Binder A)
      1 color 4x6
    - Kane, Jeffrey (Sylvere Lotringer), 1988; 185824 (Box Binder A)
      2 8x10; assorted photocopies
    - Kawada, Kikuji, 1965; 185825 (Box Binder A)
    - Liebowitz, Anne (Phillip Glass), undated; 185826 (Box Binder A)
    - Mangolte, Babette (Richard Foreman), 1977; 185827 (Box Binder A)
    - Mangolte, Babette (Stuart Sherman), undated; 185828 (Box Binder A)
    - Mangolte, Babette (Robert Wilson and Phillip Glass), 1978; 185829 (Box Binder A)
      1 7x9
    - Mangolte, Babette (Robert Wilson), undated; 185830 (Box Binder A)
      1 7x9; 3 large-format negatives
    - Mangolte, Babette, 1976; 185831 (Box Binder A)
      1 7x9; 1 8x10
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, undated; 185832 (Box Binder A)
      6 8x10
    - Myers, Rita (Barricade to Blue at the Kitchen), 1977; 185833 (Box Binder A)
      10 color slides
    - Rattray, David (Artaud translation projected at St Marks Poetry Project), 1980s; 185834 (Box Binder A)
      140 slides
    - Robinson, Theo (Mary Overlie), 1978; 185835 (Box Binder A)
    - Rose, Sheree (Dennis Cooper), undated; 185836 (Box Binder A)
      1 5x7
    - Schubert, Marcus, 1987; 185837 (Box Binder A)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Schwarz, Jeffrey (Chris Kraus), 1985; 185838 (Box Binder A)
    - [Silverthorne], Jeffrey, 1973, 1991; 185839 (Box Binder A)
    - Simon, Kate (Kathy Acker), 1986; 185840 (Box Binder A)
    - Tileston, Nathanial (Mary Overlie, et. al), undated; 185841 (Box Binder A)
    - Voigt, Reinhardt, 1983; 185842 (Box Binder A)
    - Volz, Wolfgang (Christo), undated; 185843 (Box Binder A)
    - Von Schaewen, Deidi (Rene Herbst), undated; 185844 (Box Binder A)
    - (Susan Attington, "A Happy Death"), 1989; 185845 (Box Binder A)
    - (Douglas Dunn), undated; 185846 (Box Binder A)
    - (Phillip Glass), undated; 185847 (Box Binder A)
    - (Eileen Gray), undated; 185856 (Box Binder A)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) (Chris Kraus), undated; 185857 (Box Binder A)
      4 8x10
      All items returned to donor.
    - (Steve Reich), undated; 185858 (Box Binder A)
    - (Reichstag), undated; 185859 (Box Binder A)
    - (Nancy Reilly), undated; 185860 (Box Binder A)
    - (Mallet Stevens), undated; 185861 (Box Binder A)
    - (Hans Jurgen Syberborg, as Hitler), undated; 185862 (Box Binder A)
    - Unknown Subjects, undated; 185873 (Box Binder B)
      7 8x10; 1 7x9; 5 5x7; 5 4x6; 5 color slides; 1 black and white contact sheet
    - Notes to "Christo pictures", undated; 185874 (Box Binder B)
      one large mailing envelope
  - Subseries B: Personal, 182614
    Photographic prints are arranged alphabetically by the subject's name, with unknown subjects appearing at the end. Negatives are arranged chronologically at the end of the series.
    - Cataldo, Susan, undated; 186014 (Box Binder B)
      1 black and white 3x5
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris, undated; 186015 (Box Binder B)
      8 color 3x5; 6 black and white 3x5
      Items returned to donor.
    - Lotringer, Mia, undated; 186016 (Box Binder B)
      12 colour 3x5; 1 polaroid; 1 colour 5x7; 3 black and white 8x10
    - Lotringer, Sylvere, undated; 186017 (Box Binder B)
      8 idenfication photographs; 5 colour 4x6; 2 black and white 4x6; 2 black and white 3x5; 2 black and white 5x7; 4 black and white 8x10
    - Lotringer, Sylvere and family, undated; 186018 (Box Binder B)
      2 colour 5x7 6 colour 4x6 3 black and white 4x6 4 polaroids
    - Lotringer, Sylvere and friends, undated; 186019 (Box Binder B)
      4 polaroids; 2 black and white 4x6; 4 colour 4x6
    - [Peraldi], Francois and [Scemama], Marion, 1988; 186020 (Box Binder B)
      3 color 4x6
    - Paris, Heidi, 1981; 186021 (Box Binder B)
      1 color 4x4
    - Wongpanlert, Thanya, undated; 186022 (Box Binder B)
      3 black and white 4x6
    - Unknown Subjects, undated; 186023 (Box Binder B)
      2 polaroids; 3 colour 4x6; 2 colour 3x5; 1 colour 5x7; 3 black and white 3x5; 1 black and white 4x6
    - Unknown Travel Snapshots, undated; 186024 (Box Binder B)
      27 color 4x6
    - Unknown Landscapes, undated; 186025 (Box Binder B)
      3 black and white 4x6; 4 color 4x4; 1 polaroid; 6 color 4x6
    - Ryndam, Montclair, August-September 1962; 186026 (Box Binder B)
      1 page of negatives
    - New Jersey Shore-South Bend, September 1962; 186027 (Box Binder B)
      2 pages of negatives
    - Florida, Christmas 1962; 186028 (Box Binder B)
    - United States, 1963; 186029 (Box Binder B)
      3 pages of negatives
    - Corsica, 1964; 186030 (Box Binder B)
    - Kingston, Erzurum [logements, toucuk, cheval], October-November 1965; 186031 (Box Binder B)
    - Van (lac de), January 1966; 186032 (Box Binder B)
    - Doqubeyazit; Istanbul, January 1966; April 1966; 186033 (Box Binder B)
    - Erzincan, Erzurum, Spring 1966; 186034 (Box Binder B)
    - Turkey, 1966-7; 186035 (Box Binder B)
    - Hashomez, Turkey/ USA, 1960s; 186036 (Box Binder B)
    - Athol, undated; 186037 (Box Binder B)
    - Scemama, undated; 186038 (Box Binder B)
    - Wongpanlert, Thanya, undated; 186039 (Box Binder B)
    - Unlabeled negatives, undated; 186040 (Box Binder B)
      12 pages of negatives
- Series VII: Financial Papers, 182616
  Includes files of order forms, tax returns, invoices and receipts.
  Tax and medical files are restricted and have been removed to box 60b.
  - A-E, 200771 (Box 56)
  - E-O, 200772 (Box 57)
  - O-S, 200773 (Box 58)
  - S-W, 200774 (Box 59)
  - A-T, 209549 (Box 60a)
  - RESTRICTED FILES (Taxes; Medical), 200775 (Box 60b)
- Series VIII: Clippings and Photocopies, 182615
  Contains folders of photocopies and clippings that were not labelled and could not be linked to a project elsewhere in the archive. Materials are arranged alphabetically by author's name. All miscellaneous folders are arranged chronologically at the end of the series.
  - Amery, Rex - "The Coed's Nightmare", Undated; 200782 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Appolinaire: Reprint of "Les Soirees de Paris", Undated; 200783 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - ARS Electronica Lifescience, 1999; 200784 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Art in America no. 72 - copies, Undated; 200785 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Antonin Artaud - "Lettres a Gemica Athanasiou" (1 of 2), Undated; 200786 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Antonin Artaud - "Lettres a Genia Athanasiou" (2 of 2), Undated; 200787 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Artaud photocopies, Undated; 200788 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Artaud to Jacques Riviere correspondence, Undated; 200789 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Ashby, W. Ross - "Analogie et Modeles", Undated; 200790 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Ayden, Erje - "The Crazy Green of Second Avenue" copy; with letter, 1991; 200791 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Baron - "De Nouveau sur Jacques Vache" copy, Undated; 200792 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Bataille - photocopied piece of "Oeuvres Completes de G. Bataille", Undated; 200793 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Baudelaure, Charles - "Le peintre de la nie monerne", Undated; 200794 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Baudrillard - "Le trompe l'oeil" document de travail, Undated; 200795 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Baudrillard - from "La societe de consommation", Undated; 200796 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Baudrillard - copy of "Les abimes superficiels", Undated; 200797 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Baudrillard - photocopy of "Baudrillard: Simulations", 1983; 200798 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Beatty - "Taras Polataiko", Undated; 200799 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Bhabha, Homi - copy of essay, Undated; 200800 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Blanchot - "The Last Word" copy; with annotations, Undated; 200801 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - "La Boheme" - Walter Benjamin on Baudelaire, Undated; 200802 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - [Biden] copy of "Le Secret Blanche", 1994; 200803 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Bodei - photocopy of "Discorso e verita", Undated; 200804 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Bois/Krauss - "Informe", Undated; 200805 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - "Bordercrossings" copies, 1996; 200806 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Borkhuis, Charles - copy of "Dead Men's Tails", Undated; 200807 (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Dr. Ken Brockman - "Your Whole Food Diet", Undated; 200808 (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Buchanan article - "Symptom or Diagnosis", Undated; 200809 (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Buchloh - "Richter's Facture" copy, Undated; 200810 (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Buchloh - ArtForum "Critical Reflections", 1997; 200811 (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - Burroughs - "The Devil's Bargain" copy, Undated; 200812 (Box 61, Folder 31)
  - Burroughs letter from a published book, Undated; 200813 (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - Burton, Julianne - "The Camera as 'Guh': Two Decades of Film Culture and Resistance in Latin America" copy, Undated; 200814 (Box 61, Folder 33)
  - Buyssens, Eric - "Origine de la linguistique synchronique de Saussure" copy, Undated; 200815 (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Cage, John - "For the Birds" copy, Undated; 200816 (Box 61, Folder 35)
  - Cage, John - "John Cage at Seventy-Five", Undated; 200817 (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Carrier - "Aesthete and the City", 1990; 200818 (Box 61, Folder 37)
  - Caws - "Exquisite Essentials" copy, Undated; 200819 (Box 61, Folder 38)
  - Celine - "Hommage a Zola" copy, 1963; 200820 (Box 61, Folder 39)
  - Celine - "Deathman's Dance" copy, Undated; 200821 (Box 61, Folder 40)
  - Cendrars, Blaise - piece from "The Novelist turned Reporter", Undated; 200822 (Box 61, Folder 41)
  - Clausen/Brower article - "The Confused Course of SDI", Undated; 200823 (Box 61, Folder 42)
  - Cohen, Sande - "Hide your commodification" copy, Undated; 200824 (Box 61, Folder 43)
  - "Collection Blance" book list, 1982; 200825 (Box 61, Folder 44)
  - Columbia Newspapers, Undated; 200826 (Box 61, Folder 45)
  - Cotazar - "Literature et Revolution", Undated; 200827 (Box 61, Folder 46)
  - Dali - piece from "Revolution Paranoiaque", Undated; 200828 (Box 61, Folder 47)
  - Debord - "Le detounement", Undated; 200829 (Box 61, Folder 48)
  - Debord - "Le detournement" copy, Undated; 200830 (Box 61, Folder 49)
  - Deleuze, Gilles - excerpts from "Une vie Philosophique", Undated; 200831 (Box 61, Folder 50)
  - Deleuze article in "L'autre journal", 1985; 200832 (Box 61, Folder 51)
  - "Doing It" copies, Undated; 200833 (Box 61, Folder 52)
  - Dotti - "Simone Weil, la marsigliese", Undated; 200834 (Box 61, Folder 53)
  - Durand, Regis - pages from "Disposition of the Voice", Undated; 200835 (Box 61, Folder 54)
  - East Village Eye copies, 1980's; 200836 (Box 61, Folder 55)
  - Fausto-Sterling - "How many sexes are there?", 1993; 200837 (Box 61, Folder 56)
  - Foucault - photocopy of "Interviews and other Writings", Undated; 200838 (Box 61, Folder 57)
  - "Entretien avec Michel Foucault" copy, Undated; 200839 (Box 61, Folder 58)
  - Foucault, Michel - preface copy, Undated; 200840 (Box 61, Folder 59)
  - Foucault - "Qu'est-ce qu'un auteur" copies, Undated; 200841 (Box 61, Folder 60)
  - Foucault - "Entretien avec Michel Foucault", Undated; 200842 (Box 61, Folder 61)
  - Gibson - "Johnny Mnemonic", Undated; 200843 (Box 61, Folder 62)
  - Gille, Didier and Stengers, Isabelle - "Body Fluids", Undated; 200844 (Box 61, Folder 63)
  - Giribone - Table of Contents for "La Couleur des Idees", Undated; 200845 (Box 61, Folder 64)
  - Gluck - "Jack the Modernist" copy, Undated; 200846 (Box 61, Folder 65)
  - Goddard - "France / Tour / Detour / Deux / Enfants", Undated; 200847 (Box 61, Folder 66)
  - Goldfarb, Alvin - "Theatrical activities in Nazi concentration camps" photocopy, Undated; 200848 (Box 61, Folder 67)
  - Guillerme, Jacques - "The Idea of Architectural Language: a Critical Inquiry"; with add attached, Undated; 200849 (Box 61, Folder 68)
  - Haddad, G. - "Transmission et Rites Alimentaires" copy, Undated; 200850 (Box 61, Folder 69)
  - Huelsenbeck - copy of poem "L'amiral cherche une maison a louer", Undated; 200851 (Box 61, Folder 70)
  - Jameson - "Postmodernism" copy, Undated; 200852 (Box 61, Folder 71)
  - Jameson - "Postmodernism" copy, Undated; 200853 (Box 61, Folder 72)
  - Jameson, Fredric - Interview in article, Undated; 200854 (Box 61, Folder 73)
  - Jayet - "Les Cahiers d'Aimable Jayet" copy, Undated; 200855 (Box 61, Folder 74)
  - Gradiro - "Jensen's Gradiro" in German, Undated; 200856 (Box 61, Folder 75)
  - Julien, Dominique - "Fiat Lux" copy, Undated; 200857 (Box 61, Folder 76)
  - Kaijima Foundation for the arts, 1982; 200858 (Box 61, Folder 77)
  - Kester - "The Rise and Fall of Baudrillard" copy, Undated; 200859 (Box 61, Folder 78)
  - Kosko - "Fuzzy Thinking" copies, Undated; 200860 (Box 61, Folder 79)
  - Kosuth, Joseph - "Five Recent Details" copies, Undated; 200861 (Box 61, Folder 80)
  - Kotz - "Interrogating the boundaries of women's art" copy, 1989; 200862 (Box 61, Folder 81)
  - Kunst - Article on Virilio (in German), Undated; 200863 (Box 61, Folder 82)
  - Kuspit - "Louise Bourgeois", Undated; 200864 (Box 61, Folder 83)
  - Lacan and Vincennes - "Lacan", Undated; 200865 (Box 61, Folder 84)
  - Leclaire, Serge, Undated; 200866 (Box 61, Folder 85)
  - Lejeune, Philippe - "Le pacte autobiographique" copy, Undated; 200867 (Box 61, Folder 86)
  - Les Lettres Francaise, Undated; 200868 (Box 61, Folder 87)
  - L'Étrave - Prope Doutique - Paris Lettre, undated; 201184 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Lingis "The Society of Dismembered Body Parts" copy, undated; 201185 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Livingston, Marco on Koons, undated; 201186 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Le Livres des Morts Tibétain, undated; 201187 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Lotringer interivew with Müller and Werkstatt Berlin flyer, 1988; 201188 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Lotringer/During interview - article on "French Theory", undated; 201189 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Lotringer essay on Guattari "No Comment", undated; 201190 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Lotringer "Interview with Brendan Behan, Dublin 1961 with [GPY] article in Les Lettres Françaises", undated; 201191 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Lotringer interview with Brendan Behan (for Seamus Dean) - "L'Homme Maigre", undated; 201192 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Lotringer - Brendan Behan Interviews, undated; 201193 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Lotringer - "Editorial, undated; 201194 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Lotringer - "Third Wave: Art and the Commodification of Theory" copy, undated; 201195 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Lotringer - "Agents de l'étranger" copy (history of Semiotext(e) in French), undated; 201196 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Lotringer - Two interviews with French publishers for student paper PARIS - Lettres #3 (Sorbonne), 1960 January; 201197 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Lotringer interview with Heiner Müller in Liberation, 1996; 201198 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - "Sylvere Lotringere - The Diaghilev of Deconstruction" by Andrew Olds, undated; 201199 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Lotringer - "The Game of the Name", undated; 201200 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Lotringer - "The Salut par les Juifs", undated; 201201 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Lotringer - "Gaston Ferdiéne", undated; 201202 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Lotringer "Autonomia" essay - published in Documents, mid-1980s; 201203 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - "A Conversation with Sylvere Lotringer" - photocopy of Conference 6:1, 1995; 201204 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Lotringer interview - Artscibe, undated; 201205 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Lotringer interview in Columbia magazine Conference, 1995-1996; 201206 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Lotringer published works copies, undated; 201207 (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Articles by Lotringer / about Semiotext(e), undated; 201209 (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Lotringer - "Sylvere Texts", undated; 201210 (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - Lotringer - various texts, undated; 201211 (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Lyotard photocopy of "La critique, les minorities", undated; 201212 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Lyotard - photocopy of "Energumen Capitalism", Undated; 201216 (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Lyotard photo clipped from paper, Undated; 201217 (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - Matthews, Harry - photocopy of "Lewis and Morris", Undated; 201218 (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Mayer's Restorative Art, Undated; 201219 (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - Moles "Cybernetique et Oeuvre d'Art", Undated; 201220 (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - Montreal Mirror - copy, 1987; 201221 (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - Mueller, Cookie - "I hear America Sinking", Undated; 201222 (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Muller - photocopies, Undated; 201223 (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - Myles, Eileen - "Bath, Maine", Undated; 201224 (Box 62, Folder 37)
  - Negri, Toni - "Contre le terrorisme d'Etat", November 1985; 201225 (Box 62, Folder 38)
  - The New Yorker section, Undated; 201226 (Box 62, Folder 39)
  - "No! Art" photocopies, Undated; 201227 (Box 62, Folder 40)
  - Le Nouvel Observateur - clippings, 1982; 201228 (Box 62, Folder 41)
  - Le Nouvel Observateur - clippings, 1982-1983; 201229 (Box 62, Folder 42)
  - Le Nouvel Observateur - clippings, 1983-1985; 201230 (Box 62, Folder 43)
  - O'Hara, Frank - poems, Undated; 201231 (Box 62, Folder 44)
  - Olson, Charles - "Projective Voice", Undated; 201232 (Box 62, Folder 45)
  - "Paedagogia Historica", #33, 1999; 201233 (Box 62, Folder 46)
  - Proust - "Du cote du chez Swann", Undated; 201234 (Box 62, Folder 47)
  - Rattray, David - "In Nomine", Undated; 201235 (Box 62, Folder 48)
  - Ridon - "Romance Quarterly" - Andre Breton, Undated; 201236 (Box 62, Folder 49)
  - Robin Riddles - "Beyond the Real the the Imaginary: Chris Kraus' 'How to shoot a crime' and other films", 1988; 201237 (Box 62, Folder 50)
  - Roth, M. - Knowing and History - duplicates for indexing, Undated; 201238 (Box 62, Folder 51)
  - Roth, M. - Copies of essays of "Foucault, Friend", Undated; 201239 (Box 62, Folder 52)
  - Said - "Response" Liacritics, 1973; 201315 (Box 62, Folder 53)
  - Saussure - copy of "calligrammes", Undated; 201316 (Box 62, Folder 54)
  - "Saussure in French - Struct./Post. - Spring '05", Undated; 201317 (Box 62, Folder 55)
  - Schatzman - selections from "Soul Murder", Undated; 201318 (Box 62, Folder 56)
  - Sellers, Terrence - "Taking Flight", Undated; 201319 (Box 62, Folder 57)
  - Semiotext(e) - photocopy of "Le deux Saussure" vol. 2, no.1, 1974; 201320 (Box 62, Folder 58)
  - Semiotext(e) - "Ego Traps" vol. 1, no. 3, 1975; 201321 (Box 62, Folder 59)
  - Semiotext(e) - copy of "Ego Traps" - vol. 1, no. 3, 1975; 201322 (Box 62, Folder 60)
  - Semiotext(e) - photocopy of "Forget Foucault" (Baudrillard), 1988; 201323 (Box 62, Folder 61)
  - Semiotext(e) - photocopies of "Foucault Live", Undated; 201324 (Box 62, Folder 62)
  - Semiotext(e) - copies from "Foucault Live", Undated; 201325 (Box 62, Folder 63)
  - Semiotext(e) - photocopies of original german issue, 1982; 201326 (Box 62, Folder 64)
  - Semiotext(e) - photocopies of "Polysexuality", 1981; 201327 (Box 62, Folder 65)
  - Semiotext(e) - photocopies of "Polysexuality", 1981; 201328 (Box 62, Folder 66)
  - Smith - from "Lectures on the Religion of the Semites", Undated; 201348 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Sophocles - "Oedipus the King", Undated; 201349 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Squires - "Is Richard Prince a Feminist?", Undated; 201350 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Strauss - "On Crack Wars" (Ronnell), Undated; 201351 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Tajima, Mike - printout of interview, 2009; 201352 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Tiefenbrun, Susan - copy of "La Belle Vieille de Francois Maynard", Undated; 201353 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Tillman, Lynne - copy of "Weird Fucks", Undated; 201354 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Tobin - photocopy of "New York's Jews and the Catskill Mountains", Undated; 201355 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Todorov - "How to Read", Undated; 201356 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Ullman, Stephen - "Phonologie et Point de vue Structural en Linguistique", Undated; 201357 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Urbain - "Le Toutourisme", Undated; 201358 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Village Voice Listings, July 20, 1993; 201359 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Voice Literary Supplement - Baudrillard and Deleuze clippings, Undated; 201360 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Virilio - photocopy of "The Last Vehicle", Undated; 201361 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Virilio, Paul - "Futurisme et Facsisme", Undated; 201362 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Virilio, Paul - "Esthetique Disparition", Undated; 201363 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Welchman Artforum article "Face(t)s", 1988; 201368 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Unknown author - copy of "Commen se faire un Corps sans Organes?", undated; 201369 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Unknown author - photocopies of "Architecture of Death", 1982; 201370 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Unknown editor - "Discussion of the Work", undated; 201371 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Unknown author - copies from Futurist Theory and Invention, undated; 201372 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Unknown author - "Hildegarde, Solitaire de l'Apocalypse", undated; 201373 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Unknown author - page from "Hindrance of theory in critical work", undated; 201374 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Unknown author - "Histoire de la gousse et des lunettes" and other copies with underlining, undated; 201375 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Unknown author - "Operation Desert Storm", undated; 201376 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Unknown author - "La Poverta' in Ticino" [title page], Undated; 201652 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Unknown author - "The Question of Chinese Allegory", Undated; 201653 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Unknown author - "Le Roman Americain", Undated; 201654 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Unknown author - "Situationism", Undated; 201655 (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Unknown author - "Surrealism" article, Undated; 201656 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Unknown author - "Two aspects of language and two types of aphasic disturbances", Undated; 201657 (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Unknown author - selections from "Towards a New Vocabulary", Undated; 201658 (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Unknown author - "Why Theory", Undated; 201659 (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous poems, Undated; 201660 (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous women writer's pieces, Undated; 201661 (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous zine copies, Undated; 201662 (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated; 201663 (Box 63, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated; 201664 (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated; 201665 (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated; 201666 (Box 63, Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated; 201667 (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated; 201668 (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated; 201669 (Box 63, Folder 43)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated; 201670 (Box 63, Folder 44)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated; 201671 (Box 63, Folder 45)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated; 201672 (Box 63, Folder 46)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated; 201673 (Box 63, Folder 47)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated; 201674 (Box 63, Folder 48)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated; 201675 (Box 63, Folder 49)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated; 201676 (Box 63, Folder 50)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated; 201677 (Box 63, Folder 51)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated; 201678 (Box 63, Folder 52)
  - Miscellaneous copies and clippings, Undated; 201679 (Box 63, Folder 53)